[Music]
forp Canadian
students them
[Music]
and
language b b audience high energy
without drugs so first show in Singapore
and
destroy all than to Mr every fantastic
show really
amazing used to be an actor he was agent
Smith in mrix
Revolution Mr Anderson Mr Anders a
rule
First National Museum of Singapore
[Music]
industry cultural species make
theat
this going to be fun the club
B
hello you should definitely watch
this
and that's uh Jenny right hello Jenny is
obviously taking care of the show
[Music]
today thank you so muchang you been a
[Applause]
Wonder great thing
is
almost and man
[Music]
expence
immersed Wii
WI
[Music]
univers just waiting
reaction a few moments
later
[Music]
so we just finished syon and know but
what
[Music]
is
going for Mr Spielberg set
[Music]
next
yes first time yes
[Applause]
yes
oh it be bro
damn's
get
home from the
future I'm a smart
because
show
all
matters kop was a nice
experience
yes
from The Amazing par to
mbai yes
[Music]
first
and uh we ran into this guy
hell his name is
not
[Laughter]
[Applause]
WhatsApp
[Music]
yes this more of a kids
Broad
back to the
fly back to
the thank you so very
[Applause]
much
today we are in
leerer UK one of the best Auditorium
available people thank you thank you
thank you so much thank you B for home
and
[Applause]
[Music]
everybody were enjoying being in the
moment
[Music]
leester was a it was a fun
experience
a still enjoyed the a
lot
[Music]
hey yes hi good luck good luck m
so yeah singap B
osted
by but of course you know what to do
like this video comment on this video
and share this video with your friends
and family and subscribe to the comedy f
[Music]
Factory